Greenbaum, Marcia Papers 6091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Marcia Greenbaum Papers
1981-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Greenbaum, Marcia
6091
103.5 cubic feet
103.5 linear ft.
Papers.
5793441
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6091 AV: Marcia Greenbaum Audio-Visual Materials
Arbitration, Industrial; Labor laws and legislation; Greenbaum, Marcia L.; Agawam School --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association -- Archives; Allyn and Bacon --Archives; Boston Edison Company --Archives; Boston Gear --Archives; Brookline School --Archives; Bryant Faculty Federation --Archives; Carver School --Archives; Champlain Cable --Archives; Continental Airlines Pilots Group --Archives; Crosby Valve --Archives; Flying Tiger Line --Archives; Henry Heywood Memorial Hospital --Archives; James River Corporation --Archives; John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company --Archives; Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corporation --Archives; Kraft, inc. --Archives; Leominster Hospital --Archives; Manchester Gas Company --Archives; Massachusetts Higher Education Coordinating Council --Archives; Massachusetts Teachers' Association --Archives; Massachusetts State College Association --Archives; New England Power Company --Archives; New England Telephone and Telegraph Company --Archives; New Jersey Bell --Archives; New York Telephone Company --Archives; Package Machine Company --Archives; Pan American World Airways, Inc. --Archives; Plymouth Inc. --Archives; Seaboard World --Archives; Seaboard World Airlines --Archives; Suburban Propane Corporation --Archives; Texas International Airlines Pilots Group --Archives; Transamerica Corporation --Archives; Trombly Motors --Archives; United Airlines --Archives; United Pilots -- Archives; United States Postal Service --Archives; United States. National Labor Relations Board --Archives; University of Connecticut. Board of Trustees --Archives; University of Connecticut. Professional Employees Association --Archives; Warwick School --Archives; Western Electric Company --Archives; Woonsocket School --Archives; Yale University --Archives
5793441
- Arbitration Documents: 1974 A- School Committee. (Box 1)
  - American Arbitration Association, New Bedford Sc/EA, and New Bedford School Committee AAA #1139-0005-74, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New Bedford, Mass. School Comm. and AAA#1139-005-74 Arb New Bedford Education Association A, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New Bedford, Mass. School Comm. and AAA #1139-0005-74 Arb New Bedford Education Association B (Folder 1 of 2), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New Bedford, Mass. School Comm. and AAA #1139-0005-74 Arb New Bedford Education Association B (Folder 1 of 2), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Pittsfield, Mass. School Comm. and AAA # 1139-0758-73 ARB Pittsfield, Teachers Assn., 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Pittsfield - Hearing 4/15/74, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Pittsfield- Hearing 4/16/74 RE: Montgomery, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Joint Exhibit, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Association Exhibit, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - School Committee Exhibits, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Austin Montgomery Hearing PTA and PSC Pittsfield (Folder 1 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Austin Montgomery Hearing PTA and PSC Pittsfield (Folder 2 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Austin Montgomery Hearing PTA and PSC Pittsfield (Folder 3 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Arbitration Documents: 1974 School grievances-- 1975 Braniff. (Box 2)
  - Providence, RH. IS. School Comm. and ARB Providence Teachers Union, AFT, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Quabbin, Mass. Regnl Schl Comm. and AAA # 1139-0574-74 ARB Quabbin Regional Teachers Assn. (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Quabbin, Mass. Regnl Schl Comm. and AAA # 1139-0574-74 ARB Quabbin Regional Teachers Assn., 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Torrington Company and AAA #1230 -0174-74 ARB, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Assn. of Flight Attendants, ALPA AFL-CIO Labor Studies Center Washington D.C. February 19, 1975 August 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - In the Matter of the Arbitration between Sugary Refinery Workers Local 1660 and Amstar Corporation, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Loose in Box- Amstar Corporation, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Amstar Corporation and AAA # 1130 -1263-75 ARB Sugar Refinery Workers, Local 1660, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Anderson Power Products and AAA # 1130-1120-74 ARB 1975 United Auto Workers, Local 1596, 1967-1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Arrow Automotive Industries and AAA #1130-0914-74 ARB United Auto Workers, Local 1596, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Arrow Automotive Industries Bomb Scare and AAA # 1130-0914-74 ARB United Auto Workers, Local 1596, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Avon Sole Company and AAA # 1130-1048-74 ARB 75 United Rubber Workers, Local 661, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - City of Boston, Mass. And AAA #1139-0637-75 ARB Boston Police Patrolmen's Assn., 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - City of Boston and United City, CTY, State EES N., Loc. 285 ARB 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - City of Boston and AAA # 1139-0241-75 ARB Boston Police Patrolmen's Assn., 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Boston Edison Company and Direct 1975 ARB Utility Workers of America, Local 369, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Boston Edison Company and P&M Gr. #1454 ARB 1975 Utility Workers Local No. 369, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Boston Gas Company and Direct Exp. Arb. '75 United Steel Workers of America, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Braniff International Airways and ALPA, Steward & Stewardess Div. ARB -75, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Arbitration Documents: 1975 Bridgeport-- New England. (Box 3)
  - Air Line Pilots Association S & S Division and Braniff Airways, Incorporated System Board of Adjustment, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bridgeport, Conn. Board of Education and AAA #1239-0251-75 Bridgeport Education Association (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Homer Bronson Company and AAA # 1230-0020-75 ARB United Steelworkers of A, Local 5104, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Town of Brookline, Mass. And Direct ARB 1975 Intl. Assn. of Fire Fighters, Local 950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Brown Company and UPIU, Local 75 AAA # 1130-0723-75 ARB, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Coast to Coast Construction Company and AAA #1130-0488-75 ARB United Steelworkers, Local No. 16031, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Freetown & Lakeville School Committees and AAA # 1139-0663-75 ARB Old Colony Educators Association, 1973- 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hilton Inns and AAA # 1130-0026-75 ARB Hotel & Restaurant EES. Local 277, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lexington, Mass. School Committee and AAA # 1139-1295-74 ARB 1975 Lexington Educators Assn. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Lowell Sun Publishing Company and AAA # 1130-0179-75 ARB The Newspaper Guild, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Town of Manchester, Mass. And PF 72-1975 FF Manchester Br. Of Mass. Police Assn., 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - MTA Training Seminar for PSE/AAA January 21, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Narragansett Brewing Company and AAA # 1130-0177-75 ARB Brewery Workers, Local 1114, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Narragansett Electric company and AAA # 1130-0493-75 ARB Bro. of Utility Workers Local 310, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - New England Telephone Company and AAA #1130 021075 Intl. Bro. of Elec. W., 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - New England Telephone Co. and AAA # 1130-0019-73 ARB 75 IBEW Local 22222, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - In the Matter of Arbitration between International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers and New England Telephone and Telegraph Company AAA Case No. 1130-0210-75, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Union and New England Telephone Company, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - In the Matter of: I.B.E.W., Locals 2222, 2320-27 -and- New England Telephone CO., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Arbitration Documents: 1975 New England-- United States. (Box 4)
  - New England Telephone Company and AAA # 1130-1103-74 Intl. Bro. of Elec. Wrkrs. Loc. 2222, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - State of New York SUNY and CSEA Administrative Services OER # A-190 Direct ARB 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - State of New York (Dept. of Mental Hygiene) and CSEA AAA # 1367-0094- 5-75 ARB, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - North Adams (Bd. Of Trustees of St. Coll and Kendall ARB 75 North Adams State College Assn., 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Northeast Regional Metropolitan Sch. Comm. and Direct -1975 ARB Northeast Teachers' Association (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Oxford Paper Company and AAA # 1130-0358-75 ARB United Paperworkers Intl. U, local 900 (Folder 1 of 2), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Oxford Paper Company and AAA # 1130-0358-75 ARB United Paperworkers Intl. U, local 900 (Folder 2 of 2), 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - UPIU, Local 900 -and- Oxford Paper Company AAA 1130-0358-75, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - United Paperworkers International Union Vs. Oxford Paper Company, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Putnam- Herzl Finishing Company and AAA # 1230-0028-75 ARB Connecticut Joint Board, Local 1462, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Quincy Patriot Ledger and Direct Int. ARB 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Rhode Island Board of Regents and AAA# 1139-0926-74 ARB American Assn. of University Professors, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Shenendehowa CSD, New York and AAA # 539-04123-74 ARB 1975 Shenendehowa Teachers Assn. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Silver Lake Regional School Committee and AAA # 1139-1109-74 ARB 1975 Silver Lake Regional Teachers' Assn., 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Stamford, Conn. Board of Education and AAA # 1239-0106-75 ARB Stamford Education Association, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Stop & Shop, Inc. and AAA # 1130-125175 ARB Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Local 10, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Taunton, Mass. School Committee and PS-10-1975 FF- Med. Taunton Teachers' Assn. (Administrators), 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Stop & Shop Inc. and AAA # 1130-1187-74 ARB Retail Clerks Intl. Assn., Loc. 1445, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Torrington Company and AAA # 1230-0151-75 ARB United Auto Workers, Local 1645, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Torrington Company and United Auto Workers, Local 1645 AAA # 1230-0120-75 ARB, 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - United States Postal Service and AAA # 11691-0006-75 ARB National Association of Letter Carriers, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - United States Postal Service and AAA #11691-0003-74 Ex. ARB. American Postal Workers Union, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Wayland, Mass School Committee and Wayland Teachers' Assn. 1975 Mediation, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Arbitration, Mediation, and Fact Finding: 1976 Acton, Mass.-- Marshfield. (Box 5)
  - Acton, Mass. School Committee and Direct Mediation-1976 Acton Teachers Association, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - American Airlines, Inc. and Direct ARB 1976 Transport Workers Union, Local 552 SS-101-76, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - American Airlines; Inc. Scilingo and SS-199-75 ARB 1976 Transport Workers Union Local 552, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - American Airlines, Inc. and Direct ARB SS-164-76 Rhea Transport Workers Union Local, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and AAA # 1430-0884-75 ARB 1976 Fedn. Of Telephone Workers of Pa., 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Big Y, Inc. and AMALG. Meatcutters Union; Local 33 AAA #1130-0724-76 ARB, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - City of Boston and Boston Police Patrolmen's Assn. AAA #1139-1704-75 ARBB1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - City of Boston, Mass. And Boston Public Library EES. AAA #1139-1738-75 ARB 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - City of Boston and United City; Cty, St EES, Local 285 AAA #1139-0087-76 ARB, 1969-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - City of Boston and Boston Police Superior Officers Assn. AAA #1139-0348-76 ARB, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - City of Boston, Mass. And Boston Police Patrolmen's Assn. AAA #1139-1700-75 ARB 76, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - ]City of Boston and Boston Police Patrolmen's Assn. AAA #1139-0245-76 ARB 1976, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - City of Boston and Boston Police Superior Officers Assn. AAA #1139-0636-75 et al 0240-76 0429-76 0501-76 0245-76, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Boston School Committee and Boston Teachers' Union AFT AAA #1139-0371-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Boston School Committee and Boston Teachers' Union AAA #1139-1528-75 ARB 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Boston Edison Company and Utility Workers Local 369 P&M Grievance 1543 Direct ARB 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Boston Edison Company and Utility Workers Un. Of America, Loc. 36 P&M Gr. 1591 Direct 1976 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Boston Gas Company and United Steelworkers of America Re: Senior Adjuster, 1972-1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Boston Whaler; Inc. and General Teamsters Union Local 653 AAA #1130-1618-76 ARB, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Town of Brookline, Mass. And Brookline Branch of Mass. Police Assn. Direct ARB 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Town of Brookline Mass. And Staff Association of the Public Library Direct-ARB-76, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Cambridge Thermionic Corp. and United Electrical; R &MW, Local 262 AAA#1130-1858-75 ARB 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Carpenter & Paterson, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America AAA #1130-0397-76 ARB, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cerro Wire & Cable Company and Intl. Bro. of Elec. W. Local 1370 AAA #1230 0319-75 ARB 1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Cheshire, Conn. Bd. Of Education and Cheshire Education Association AAA #1239-0259-75 ARB, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Draper Laboratory, Inc. and Res. Dev. & Technical EES Union AAA #1130-0034-76 ARB 1976 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Eastern Container Corp. and I.U.E., Local 284 AAA # 1130-1564-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - eyelet Specialty Company, Inc. and United Steelworkers. Local 8289 AAA #1230-0350-76 ARB, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Fernandes Super Markets, Inc. and Southeast Food Handlers U. Local 4 AMC AAA #1130-0466-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Gorton Corporation and Seafood District Local No. 15 Direct ARB 1976 FMCS 76K 25549, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Gulf & Western Inds. Eagle Signal Div. and United Auto Workers, Local 1596 AAA # 1130-1821-75 ARB 1976 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Gulf & Western Co. Systems Eagle Signal and United Auto Workers, Local 1596 AAA #1130-1355-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Industrial Relations Research Assn. 1976 Annual Meeting Sept. 16-18 Atlantic City, New Jersey (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - ITT Continental Baking Co. and Intl. Assn. of Machinists. D. L. No. 38 AAA #1130-1423-76 ARB, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Maine MSAD #24 Board of Directors and Van Buren, Maine Education Association AAA #1139-0048-76 ARB, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Maremont Corp. and Textile Workers, Local 406 FMCS RE 76K06975 ARB 76, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Marshfield School Committee and Marshfield Teachers' Assn. AAA # 1139-0799-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Arbitration, Mediation, and Fact Finding: 1976 Mass. Ed.-- Wyman. (Box 6)
  - Mass. BD. Of Trustees of State Colleges and Worcester State College Fac. FEDN. AAA #1139-0909-76 ARB, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - M.B.T.A. and Off. & Prf.. EES Un. ARB- Direct 1976 Local 453 Senior Buye, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Merriman, Inc. and Intl. Assn. of Machinists. Local #38 AAA #1130-0416-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Natick School Committee and Natick Teachers' Assn. Direct- ARB-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - New England Petroleum Co. and Teamsters, Local No. 59 Direct ARB 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and Telephone Workers Union, Local 827 TBEW AAA #1330-0384-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - City of Newton, Mass. And Newton Police Association AAA #1139-0452-76 ARB, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - State University of New York Downstate Medical Center and CSEA. Inc. AAA #1367-0228-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - New York State Univ. Construction Fund and Nysperb A76-1 ARB 1976 Civil Service Employees Asssn., Inc. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - State of New York (Dept. of Mental Hyg. And AAA #1367-0204-76 ARB Letch Civil Service Employees Assn. Worth, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - SUNY State University of New York and Operational EES @ Buffalo. CSEA OER #A-288 Direct 1976 ARB (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - SUNY St. University of New York and United University Professions, NYSUT AAA #13672-0001-76--ARB, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Noble Hospital and Licensed Practical Nurses of Mass. Inc. AAA #1130-0954076 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Norfolk, Conn. Board of Education and Norfolk Educators' Assn. AAA #1239-0311-73 ARB 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ocean Spray Cranberries and INTD. Bro. of Teamsters, Local 653 FMCS 76K08680 ARB 1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Park Hill Manor Nursing Home and Service EES Intl. Un, Local 495 AAA # 1130-0801-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Perin Products Corporation and I.U.E.; Local 259, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Randy Manufacturing Company and United Rubber Workers. Local 993 AAA #1130-0514-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - State of Rhode Island and Howard Union of Teachers AAA #1139-1595-75 ARB 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Rice Barton Corporation and United Steelworkers of America AAA #1130-1403-76 ARB, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Seymour, Conn. Board of Education and Seymour Education Association AAA #1239-0167-76 ARB, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Shelton, Conn. Board of Education and Shelton Federation of Teachers. AFT AAA #1239-0133-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Spaulding Moss Westwood and Graphic Arts Intl. Union. Local. 300 AAA #1130-064-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - St. Margret's Hospital for Women and AAA #1130-1801-75 ARB 76 Hospital & Public Employees Union, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Stop & Shop Companies, Inc. and American AMALG. Security & Watchman's U AAA #1130-0626-76 ARB, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Stop & Shop, Inc. and Retail Clerks Intl Assn. Local 1450 AAA #1130-1350-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Torrington Company and United Auto Workers; Local 1645 AAA #1230-0069-76 ARB, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Torrington Company United Auto Workers, Local 1645 AAA #1230-0006-76 ARB, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Torrington Company and United Auto Workers, Local 1645 AAA #1230-0132-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Torrington Company and United Auto Workers, Local 1645 AAA #1230-0070-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Torrington Company and United Auto Workers, Local 1645 AAA #1230-0218 75 ARB 1976 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Town of Trumbull, Conn. And Conm. Council of Police Unions #15 AAA #1239-0043-76 ARB, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - United States Postal Service and America Postal Workers Union AAA #11691-0012-76 ARB 1976 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - U.S. Postal Service and Natl. Assn. of Letter Carriers AAA #11691-0021-75 Exp. ARB 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - United States Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union AAA #11691-0009-76 Exp. ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Van Norman Company and I.U.E.. Local 213 AAA #1130-0399-76 ARB, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - West End Iron Works and Ironworkers: Local 501 Discharge Direct ARB 1976 FMCS (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Western Massachusetts Electric Company and Intl. Bro. of Elec. W.; Local 455 Direct ARB 1976 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - vWyman- Gordon Company and United Steelworkers of America AAA #1130-0865-76 ARB, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Arbitration, Mediation, and Fact Finding: 1977 American Air--Commonwealth Gas. (Box 7)
  - American Airlines, Inc. and Transport Workers Union, Local 552 88-66-77 ARB Eliz. Thurston, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - American Airlines, Inc. and Transport Workers Union Local.552 SS-17-77 ARB Sharon Griffin, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - American Biltrite Rubber Co. and United Rubber Workers, Local 209 AAA #1130-0794-77 ARB 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - AMBAC Industries, Inc. I.U.E. Local 206 FMCS # 77K06061 ARB 1977, 1962-1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - American Bultrite, Inc.and URWA, Local 25 AAA #1130-1673-76 ARB 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Anderson Power Products and United Auto Workers; Local 1596 AAA #1130-0818-77 ARB 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Armstrong Corp.. And DALU Local 22619 FMCS # 76K24346 RB 1977, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Arrown Automotive Industries and United Auto Workers: Local 1596 AAA #1130-0296-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore Brushes and E.E.; Local 262 AAA #1130-1210-77 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Borden, Inc. Chemical Division and Intl. Chemical Workers Union; Local 553 FMCS # 77K13484 ARB 1977, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Town of Arlington Mass and MBC and A PF 53 1977 Int Atb. Arlington Police (Folder 1 of 3), 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Town of Arlington Mass and MBC and A PF 53 1977 Int Atb. Arlington Police (Folder 2 of 3), 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Scope and Contents
    1977 Annual Report and 1978-1979 Performance Budget
  - Town of Arlington Mass and MBC and A PF 53 1977 Int Atb. Arlington Police (Folder 3 of 3), 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - City of Boston and Boston Police Patrolmen's Assn. AAA #1139-1168-77 ARB, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - City of Boston and Boston Police Superior Officers AAA #1139-1007-77 ARB, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - City of Boston, Dept. of Health & Hosp. and Service Employees Intl. Un.. Local 285 AAA # 1139-0105-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Boston Edison Company and UMUA; Local 369 P&M #1528 Direct RB 1977, 1975-1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Boston Whaler; Inc. and Teamsters, Local 653 AAA #1130-0212-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Town of Brookline and Brookline Br. Of Mass. Police Assn. Direct ARB 1977 Blair & Miller (Folder 1 of 2), 1973- 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Town of Brookline and Brookline Br. Of Mass. Police Assn. Direct ARB 1977 Blair & Miller (Folder 2 of 2), 1973- 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Town of Brookline, Mass. And Brookline Police Assn. ARB Direct 1977 Uniform allowance, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Butler - Aviation- Boston, Inc. and IAMAW. Air Transport District #41 AAA #1130-0142-77 ARB 1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Cape Cod Hospital and Massachusetts Nurses Assn. AAA #1130-0737-77 ARB 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Central Maine Power Company- Mason Sta. and Intl. Bro. of Elec. Work; Local 1837 ARB Direct 1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Clark- Cutler- McDermott Co. and AMAL. CLO. Tex. W U, Local 31 AAA #1130-0492-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Colonnade Hotel and Hotel & Restaurant EES, Local 26 ARB District 1977 Parking right, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Columbia Electronics (AVNET Co.) and United Elec. Rad & Mach W. L Local 219 Direct RB 1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Commonwealth Gas Company and United Steelworkers, Local 120004 Direct ARB 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Arbitration, Mediation, and Fact Finding: 1977 Coventry-- Meyer, G.. (Box 8)
  - Coventry, RH. IS. School Committee and Coventry Teachers Alliance AAA #1139-1767-76 ARB 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - O.K. Faarbaks, Inc. and AMAL. Meat Cutters &BWNA, Local 10 AAA #1130-1037-77 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - GAF Corporation and UP&AW, IBT, Teamsters Local 735 AAA #1130-0565-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Gas Service Inc. Nashua, N.H. and USA Direct ARB 1977, 1969-1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)